If you have created offers online, you
know that having the right photo to
match your landing page is often what
makes or breaks the emotion and the
connection that you make with people. If
you have a lead magnet, if you have a
free course, if you have a paid course,
having photos on that landing page is
one of the number one things that really
adds spice to it. But a lot of people
don't know how to do that. They don't
have great photos. They don't know how
to illustrate things or do stuff like
that. Well, the beauty is now with
artificial intelligence, we have so much
access to tools to create photos at our
disposal. Just between chat GPT and Gro
alone, those two right there, the
lifelike ability to create perfect
images for any scene is incredible. And
as well, if you use a tool like
Higsfield, which I'm a big fan of using
Higsfield, you can also do lifelike
photos of yourself or things like that.
Do a digital photo shoot type of a
thing. So, I want to show you kind of
how I I would use this for different
landing pages and offers that we have.
I'm going to show you an example. We
have an offer right now that I'm
running. You can find a link in the
description below if we're still running
this at the time you're watching this
video
to a $5 course uh all about Instagram
ads. It's this $54.95 course on what to
do when running Instagram ads. And I
used AI to help me write the copy here.
I now this is actually a real photo of
me right there. Um this is an AI
generated photo right here. But what I
would like to do is possibly update a
few of these different photographs. And
so what I would do is let's say I have
no photos on this page.
I want to take this section and this
section right here. And what I'll do is
I will go into chat GPT
and I'm going to say to chat GPT, let's
just use instant for this. Uh, describe
a happy photo of a scene
for a landing page with sales copy
to go along with this of
the subject,
the speaker, author
to match the sales copy for the landing
page. Okay. So, we're going to take the
landing page copy. We're going to type
that in there. And then we're actually
going to have it create a description of
a photo right here.
There we go. This is actually This is
great.
Okay.
So, now if I take this into like
Higsfield right here, I can go under
create an image.
Paste this in here. this description
generate. Maybe I'll generate two
versions of this and it's going to
generate this for me. Now, I actually
have an AI that's trained in Higsfield
on uh my photos that I can actually see
this. And so, like right here, Higsfield
has so many different tools for video um
and image creation. It's probably one of
the best all-in-one tools for the price.
It just gives you so much amazing
different tools, and it's one of the
easiest to use, one of the best priced
as far as just lots of crazy image and
video type things. Uh, but they have
this thing
called
Higsfield Soul. And Higsfield Soul
allows you to create characters. It's
like we have one for my mom right here,
but we have this one for me right here.
And so to create a character, you have
to basically upload photos, up to 20
photos that fit this style into here.
And their AI will then go in and create
a character that you can use to generate
images. And it's very fast at generating
these images. So like it's going to
generate these images right here.
It's going to create these.
And you know what's another thing too is
we could actually generate this
Uh let's see. Generate this image and
generate an image right here.
Okay.
And see what this generates with Grock
for an image
generation right there. Okay. So there's
an image uh right there. If we use grock
imagine,
we could see multiple versions of these
images right here.
Okay.
So, this is actually this is great. This
is doing that. That's what the Grock
algorithm is doing. Now, that's a woman.
Let's see if we do this. Uh, make this a
man.
Okay.
So, we could make it a man right here
and then bring this into Higsfield. So,
like here's what it generated for me
inside of Higsfield. Now, the body
doesn't necessarily match, but the the
face is pretty good. So, then what I
would do is I might throw a few of these
in here, and I'm going to change it. I
say add a white backwards
baseball cap. Uh, make the guy
a bit uh larger
just to make it realistic. Um,
and add glasses. And so I might generate
a couple versions of this with uh with
with that description as well. Okay. So
like here's one with with a man right
here. If I wanted it to like look like
one of these images right here, I could
just literally paste this into Higsfield
and upload an image as the prompt.
So, let me say like this is right here.
Okay. So, we're going to download that,
save that to the computer.
Then, we're going to upload this image,
and it's going to make a version of that
image, but with me as the character that
looks just like that image. Here's
another version right here. This is what
ChatGBT created. This one's actually
probably the best style of a stock
image, though, I would say.
And that's actually a lot closer to what
I would even prefer. Oh, look. I can
just copy and paste the image in here.
That's great. I don't even need to
upload it. This is like the more of the
the the layout that I would even prefer
if it could create for my image. And
then I can just add the like I said, the
backward baseball cap and all that into
this. So, let's see what this does.
for this. Okay, so these are just tools
that I love to use to generate stock
images. You can make an image of anybody
using a combo like chat GBT and Grock to
either come up with the style, the
theme, describe it, and you can make
images of yourself using Higsfield. You
can make realistic images of a random
person in Higsfield. All
right, let's see what this generates.
Here we go.
Okay, that one actually does look a lot
more like me right there.
If I was to use that one, that might
that might be a style that I might use.
This one's pretty good. That one's
pretty good.
I like that.
Okay.
Now, what I want to see is I want to see
how it was able to translate
those other photos that we uploaded.
Okay. So, there's that one right there.
Um, let's see. Make the guy a bit
larger.
White backwards
baseball cap and glasses on.
It's just going to It's just going to
look more like me. Um, if we do that,
you know.
So, there we go.
Different versions
right here. So, like with the ba the
baseball cap and the
the photo,
it's not going to be perfect, but it's
going to get to where it's like
close enough. These are funny. It's like
it threw uh my face onto the guy to kind
of make that. So anyways, that's what
you can do for things like that. If you
wanted to generate like just a photo for
like for a scene or something like that.
Let's say I want to have
uh okay, describe a photo for this part
of the landing page with two business
owners.
Um, let's do this. Let's describe like
another photo. Here's a description in
like the what you discover section.
There we go.
Cool. Okay, let's throw this into Gro
imagine
and see what this generates right here.
I love Grock Imagine because it's just
so quick at generating these images.
Uh, and I could tell chat GBT, uh,
generate this image for me.
And I'll even throw in like create image
mode.
We go. Okay, there's Grock.
They look a little too intimate in that
one right there. Yeah, these these look
like um,
[laughter] how would I say? Uh, if
they're not married, these are like uh
HR, how to get in trouble at the
workplace type images.
>> [laughter]
>> These look like dating photos. How to
date your coworker. Like that. Isn't
that the vibe? That's That's hilarious.
Um, make it look less
intimate like they are dating and have
them look into the camera. [laughter]
That's funny. It's almost there. But
yeah, that definitely is like, oh, like
you want to go out for drinks and dinner
afterwards. Like, yeah,
definitely.
Okay, these are looking a little bit
better.
It's still got It's like find somebody
who looks at you like she's looking at
the character right there. That's so
funny.
This one's pretty good right here.
This style. And if you don't want like
suits, you know, you could even use um
this style.
make them more casual and look at the
camera. So, that's why I like Grock
imagine because it kind of lets you like
really
play around and branch through different
ideas.
Um,
and things like that. So, yeah, not
perfect, but
there's some ideas. Okay, this is See,
this is better.
Something like this.
just kind of like describing that. Let's
say we threw something into Higsfield
and we told it to just generate an image
like these characters.
That's another thing that we can do. We
can just generate an image like the
characters that we're using
in Higsfield. And these are just like
different ways of coming up with stock
images. You could brainstorm different
scenes and things like this. Um,
let's see.
Looks a bit too much like a workplace
dating
dating photo. Let's stick to business.
Remake the prompt. Let's try that. Okay.
So, like you could argue that the prompt
isn't exactly what we're looking for and
then start to regenerate the uh images.
That first set from Grock, man, was uh
that was uh
HR is gonna they're going to get called
into HR for those for sure.
Um
see,
sorry, phone's not on silent.
All right. So, it's generating those new
images right there.
This is generating image and Brock is
Oh, Grock decided to.
Oh, you know what? Yes. The thing with
Grock is
it's not going to take an image as
input. It's going to
try to dis
make it a video. That's right.
All right. Let's see what Higsfield was
able to kind of take the chat GBT1 and
do. So, anyways, for like a landing page
like this, and I, you know, I think I
might update my character right here, my
my people right here. I mean, they look
they look that's a good very like
realistic. This is kind of the vibe I
was more going for. But
so these are all uh images that I could
put on this landing page right here that
better tell the story of what the offer
is overall.
And so if you're creating a landing
page, you're creating offers and you
don't have stock images or things like
that, using tools like this is really
useful. Um, there's another tool I love
called PO. It's $20 a month. I use it
for everything and they have all kinds
of bots and things like that that you
can use. Uh, image generation bots,
every like tons of different image
generation algorithms, video generation
bots, things like that that you could
also use uh in there.
So if you are somebody who is
building your business, you want to know
how to have the right image for maybe
your social media content, your landing
page, your ads, your offers, things like
that. Utilizing ChatGpt, Grock.
I would say those are probably the two
best ones that I use for images like
like photographic type images. Uh
Higsfield for you know the use case of
like realistic photos of you type of a
thing.
you can't go wrong. Uh and it and it you
can get all your images knocked out in
less than 30 minutes, even less than 15
minutes for any landing page. So, if
you're struggling to know like what
image you have uh or what to do, you can
do that. Okay. The other thing too is
you could even change the style. Like
let's say we go into Grock right here.
We'll go into imagine.
We're going to do Here's an image right
here. We're going to say now make this
an exaggerated CGI
characters
like a Pixar movie. Okay. So, this is
this would like change the style to like
a Pixar movie type thing. If you want to
have sort of more of like a fun
feel or theme to your images, you could
do this as well. See that?
These are actually great. These are
really cool.
The That's kind of awkward how it did
how it did that, but yeah. So, again,
really cool kind of ways of doing this
there. There's unlimited potential when
it comes to the types of images that you
can come up with. And the free version
of Grock
uh can do this. So can uh Chat GBT, but
I think it's worth the investment as
well. And then Higsfield is just really
cool at kind of come up with stuff like
this. Oh, here we go. Oh, the Higsfield
images actually came out really nice
as far as like the the setting and the
quality and all that. How it was able to
kind of go in and
really
hone in on
the the type of people. So, it was able
to like really come up with a great type
of photo for this. These are actually
really quality right here as well. This
is awesome. So, yeah. See, you see the
value of Higsfield as far as quality
photographs as well. You can't go wrong
with that. Listen, if you're wanting to
grow your coaching business, mentoring
business, uh my wealthy coach academy
program is one of the best programs
that's out there for building an online
coaching mentoring business. And so I'd
love to have you become a part of it. I
have a brand new class all about
Instagram ads. It's in the description
below. You can check that out and that
will help you get into our program as
well quickly. I'd love to work with you.
We'll talk with you soon. Have a good
one. Make sure you subscribe.